[Music]
spider in a glider
by leslie simms when you hear this sound
turn the page spider is spinning her
sparkling strings swaying from branches
she sings as she swings
i wish to fly so i'm making some wings
[Music]
she creeps up a rock and then leaps into
space
what a shock with a splat she lands
flat on her face
[Music]
i'll try it again i will fly
declare spider she falls even harder
but beetle has spied her
i can't fly either size beetle beside
her
though i tried and i tried
so i built my own glider
the glider is gleaming and ready to ride
beetle and spider both clamber inside
dragonfly toes them up high in the sky
then beetle let's go we are flying
bye bye
they glide in wide circles and ride on
the
breeze the wind blows below them